Guide to the Yale College, Class of 1940, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale College, Class of 1940, records
1946-2001
RU 391
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1
(2 boxes)
The records consist of the class secretary's files and a brochure documenting a war memorial scholarship sponsored by the Yale College Class of 1940.
Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1940
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 10-A (YRG 10-A), Records of Yale College classes.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of the class secretary's files and a brochure documenting a war memorial scholarship sponsored by the Yale College Class of 1940.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1940; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae
- Class of 1940 War Memorial Scholarship brochure, 1946; Accession 1998-A-096
  - Class of 1940 War Memorial Scholarship brochure, 1946 (Box 1)
- Records of the secretary of the Class of 1940, 1990-2000; Accession 2002-A-059; 1; (2 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  No inventory available.
  - Correspondence, class of 1940, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, class of 1940, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, class of 1940, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, class of 1940, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, class of 1940, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, class of 1940, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, class of 1940, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, class of 1940, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 60th reunion, class of 1940, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Records of William Field as secretary, class of 1940, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 45th reunion, class of 1940, Dick Jordan memorial service, widows, miscellaneous from classmates, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)